<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on CAPSTONE</title>
    <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on CAPSTONE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/university-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/university-support/</guid>

      <description>University Support #  Supporting Young Innovative Students 🎓 #  Innopolis University, a renowned institution known for its focus on technology and innovation, is not only dedicated to academic excellence but also strives to empower and support young entrepreneurs in their pursuit of turning their innovative ideas into successful startups. By providing coaching, expertise across different domains, and invaluable networking opportunities, Innopolis University plays a vital role in nurturing the next generation of entrepreneurial leaders.</description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week #1</title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_1/</guid>

      <description>Week #1 #  Introduction #  Important Note
This blog serves as a central platform for important updates and information regarding our project journey. It is vital that you regularly check this blog for the latest updates and announcements. The content provided on this blog is intended for informational purposes only and may be subject to change without prior notice.  Week #1 is the most crucial week of the entire semester as it sets the foundation for your project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/special-economic-zone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/special-economic-zone/</guid>

      <description>Special Economic Zone #  As many of you know, Innopolis is home to a Special Economic Zone (SEZ) that offers a range of benefits and services for IT companies and R&amp;amp;D projects. Whether you are a student start-up, a small or medium enterprise, or a large corporation, there are suitable office spaces, tax incentives, recruitment support, and access to a talented pool of specialists. Once you&amp;rsquo;ve gained a recognition from the University Startup Board - you can apply for support from the SEZ and use their network and resources to gain additional momentum on your startup</description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week #2</title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_2/</guid>

      <description>Week #2 #  Important Note

We hope you had a fantastic start to the project and sailed through the first week with flying colors! If you come across any hiccups or have any questions, please don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to reach out to us. We&amp;rsquo;re here to support you every step of the way, ensuring that you and your team stay on track and deliver outstanding results. Together, let&amp;rsquo;s make this journey a resounding success!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week #3</title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_3/</guid>

      <description>Week #3 #  Important Note
Please, wait for the update  </description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week #4</title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_4/</guid>

      <description>Week #4 #  Important Note
Please, wait for the update  </description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week #5</title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_5/</guid>

      <description>Week #5 #  Important Note
Please, wait for the update  </description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week #6</title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_6/</guid>

      <description>Week #6 #  Important Note
Please, wait for the update  </description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week #7</title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/weekly-tasks/week_7/</guid>

      <description>Week #7 #  Important Note
Please, wait for the update  </description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/investment-and-venture-fund-of-the-republic-of-tatarstan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/investment-and-venture-fund-of-the-republic-of-tatarstan/</guid>

      <description>IVFRT - Investment and Venture Fund of the Republic of Tatarstan #  The Investment and Venture Fund of the Republic of Tatarstan (IVFRT) is a government-backed fund that supports innovation and entrepreneurship in the region. Established in 2004, the fund has invested in more than 450 projects in various sectors, such as chemical, industrial, and technological. The fund also provides grants, loans, and leasing mechanisms for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), as well as organizes contests, events, and programs to foster the development of new ideas and technologies.</description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FASIE</title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/fasie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/fasie/</guid>

      <description>Foundation for Assistance to Small Innovative Enterprises #  The Foundation for Assistance to Small Innovative Enterprises in Science and Technology (FASIE) is a state non-profit organization that supports the development and innovation of small businesses in the scientific and technical sphere. It was established by the decree of the Government of the Russian Federation on February 3, 1994. The main tasks of FASIE are to implement the state policy of fostering and supporting science and technology, to create and develop the infrastructure for assistance, to create new jobs for the effective use of the scientific and technical potential of Russia, to provide financial, informational and other help, to involve young people in innovative activities, and to attract non-budgetary investments in the sphere of small innovative entrepreneurship.</description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MTS Venture Fund</title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/mts-venture-fund/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/mts-venture-fund/</guid>

      <description>MTS Venture Fund #  MTS Venture Fund is a venture capital fund that invests in early-stage startups in various sectors such as fintech, edtech, entertainment, IoT, and cloud. The fund is managed by MTS StartUp Hub, a division of MTS, Russia’s largest mobile phone-carrier and AI research center. The fund aims to help startups grow faster with unique access to the MTS ecosystem and its expertise in artificial intelligence, data analysis, and digital solutions.</description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Entities</title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/other-entities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/startup-support/other-entities/</guid>

      <description>Which support can we get? #  Starting a business as a student can be an exciting yet challenging endeavor. Fortunately, there is a wealth of support available to help student startups thrive and turn their innovative ideas into successful ventures. In this post, we will explore the various types of venture support and other resources that student startups can tap into.
  University-Based Incubators and Accelerators: Many universities have established incubators and accelerators specifically designed to support student entrepreneurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/groups/jurnalik/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/groups/jurnalik/</guid>
      <description>Jurnalik #   Jurnalik is a mobile application, an electronic &amp;ldquo;newspaper&amp;rdquo; that collects and provides the user with the latest news, posts and photos from their social networks, news channels and subscriptions in one application.
Week 1. The Beginning #  Team Formation and Project Proposal #  Team Members #     Team Member Telegram ID Email Address     Nikita Semeritskiy  @FatM1nd  n.</description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/groups/the-laughing-hippos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/groups/the-laughing-hippos/</guid>

      <description>The Laughing Hippos #  This is the page for your group to write reports following the lectures and weekly tasks:
Hi! We a group called &amp;ldquo;The Laughing Hippos&amp;rdquo; and we do the &amp;hellip;
Example #  Est in vagis et Pittheus tu arge accipiter regia iram vocatur nurus. Omnes ut olivae sensit arma sorori deducit, inesset crudus, ego vetuere aliis, modo arsit? Utinam rapta fiducia valuere litora adicit cursu, ad facies</description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/groups/the-smiling-boars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/groups/the-smiling-boars/</guid>

      <description>The Smiling Boars #  This is the page for your group to write reports following the lectures and weekly tasks:
Hi! We a group called &amp;ldquo;The Wild Boars&amp;rdquo; and we do the &amp;hellip;
Example #  Est in vagis et Pittheus tu arge accipiter regia iram vocatur nurus. Omnes ut olivae sensit arma sorori deducit, inesset crudus, ego vetuere aliis, modo arsit? Utinam rapta fiducia valuere litora adicit cursu, ad facies</description>

    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/hidden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://capstone-pr.netlify.app/docs/weekly-tasks/hidden/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
